wheelsnext.com 2009-06-27

# Privacy Policy - Wheels Rims Tires for Cars Trucks SUVs WheelsNext.com

Toll Free Experts: 1-866-937-6398 | Phone Hours (EST) MON-FRI: 9am - 9pm SAT: 10am - 6pm 

### Privacy Policy

| About the Policy  
---  
Wheelsnext.com is committed to respecting the privacy rights of our customers and all visitors to our web site. We take this matter very seriously, and have instituted many policies and procedures to insure that none of your privacy rights as stated herein are ever violated. The following outlines Wheelsnext.com's privacy policy and details the measures we have taken to safeguard and protect your privacy, while providing you with a unique and rewarding online shopping experience. By visiting Wheelsnext.com you are agreeing to the policies detailed below.  

Electronic Communications  
When you send an email to Wheelsnext.com or visit the web site, you are communicating with us electronically. When you send an email to Wheelsnext.com, you consent to receive communications from us electronically in response. Please note that this does not constitute opting in to our email or direct mail lists. Wheelsnext.com may communicate with you by email, by updating or posting notices on the web site. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosure and other communications that Wheelsnext.com provides to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communication be in writing. All communications with Wheelsnext.com become the property of Wheelsnext.com.  

Personal Information  
Your information is used to process your orders and personalize your shopping experience on Wheelsnext.com, for internal purposes and to comply with any legal requirements. By storing your personal information on a secure server, Wheelsnext.com is able to shorten your checkout process and allow you to check your order status online.  

Safeguards  
Wheelsnext.com has implemented a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information supplied by you is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and securely stored in Wheelsnext.com's database.  

Removing Your Name  
To have your email address removed from our list of addresses that receive information about new products, service, sales and promotions, simply email us at unsubscribe@wheelsnext.com. PLEASE NOTE: It can take up to 3 business days to process this request so you may get another email from us. Thank you in advance for your understanding.  

Consent  
You acknowledge that this privacy policy is part of the terms of service and you agree that using this site signifies your assent to Wheelsnext.com's privacy policy. Wheelsnext.com reserves the right to change the terms of service, including this privacy policy, at any time, without advanced notice. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.  

Questions or Comments  
If you have any questions or comments please e-mail us at [customerservice@wheelsnext.com](mailto:customerservice@wheelsnext.com)
